So friends, IIC Lord has disclosed its quarter
three numbers, so
let's see what is there. In the quarter three
numbers, the data is physically given to the company
in lakhs. I will convert it to crores and
explain what happened. If we
talk about the last quarter, the
total income of the company in the last quarter was
around Rs 5049 crores, last year it was
around Rs 4362 crores, whereas if we look at it now,
you have seen the total income of the company around Rs 53 crores. So, if we
look at it year after year, you have seen the
total income of the company increasing year after year. If you
look at it,
you will see approximations. However, if we
go quarter to quarter, there is
a slight decline in the total income of the company quarter to quarter. We
can say a slight
decline of around Rs 1,000, we will not call it a decline, we will
call it almost flat. So, if we
look at it quarter to quarter, the
total income of the company is almost flat,
but if we look at it year to year, we are
seeing a significant increase. Let's
look at the net premium income of the company
because the company  The main revenue of the company is being
generated from there only.
In the last quarter, the company had generated Rs 6272 crores as against Rs
5599 crores last year. Now, if you look at the
total interest income of the company, it has
increased to around Rs 6436 crores. If
you pay attention here, then the
interest income of the company, which is the
net premium income, has been
seen increasing quarter by quarter,
whereas the net income has
fallen slightly quarter by quarter. But if you
look at the main source from where the company's revenue is generated, then the company has
seen an increase, which is positive here.
Let's see what are the expenses of the company. If we talk about the
last quarter, then the
total expenses of the company in the last quarter were around Rs 4452 crores, last
year Rs 4085 crores. Now, if you look at the company's expenses,
you have seen around Rs 4587 crores. So, the
expenses of the company have been seen to be very high in this quarter.
Yes, the expenses of the company are controlled to a great extent, which means the
company is controlling it.  The company has incurred a lot of expenses in this quarter,
due to which you can see the company's profit
struggling a bit.
Talking about the last quarter, the
profit in the last quarter was Rs 577 crore.
Last year it was around Rs 352 crore. If we look at it now, the
company's profit is around Rs 431 crore.
Yes, if we
look at it year after year, you can see a significant increase in the company's profit year after year. If we look at the
approximates, then you can see
a big decline in the company's profit quarter after quarter. If we look at it
also, let's look at the
approximates.
What changes did
you see in EPS? Let's also look at the NPA. So, if we
talk about EPS, then see,
in the last quarter the company's EPS was ₹1.75 paise.
Last year it was ₹7718 paise. If we look at it now, it is
around 878 paise. So, if we look at the EPS, it has been
increasing year after year,
but if we look at it quarter after quarter, then
you can see a slight decline in the EPS. Let's see the
company  Let us
see what is Gross NP Net NP of the company, so
basically the section of Gross NP Net NP of the company has
not been disclosed here by the company, so let us leave it,
otherwise if we look at the overall numbers, then the
numbers are good year after year, year after year
you can see the revenue of the company and the profit of the company both increasing in a great manner,
but if we
go on quarterly basis, then the results of the company on quarterly basis are a
bit disappointing to you, so that's all
for today, if you liked the video then please like it and also
subscribe to the channel,
thank you.